## WANG JICHEN

Web: https://jichen.pb.online/resume Email: jichenw@andrew.cmu.edu

Tel: (412) 539-7087

## **SUMMARY**

A passionate architecture graduate student with 1 year internship experience in Playze architecture consultant company in Shanghai. Won excellent graduation design (the 1st place) of Shanghai Jiaotong University. Hard-working and responsible. Desire to become a creative architect after graduation.

	EDUCATION
Carnegie Mellon University   Pittsburgh, US   Master of Advanced Architectural Design Major GPA: 3.72/4.0   STEM	08.2018—05.2020
Italy Sapienza University of Rome   Rome, Italy Top Architecture and Arts Summer Workshop	07.2016—08.2016
Shanghai Jiao Tong University   Shanghai, China   Bachelor of Architecture Major GPA: 3.93/4.0   Ranking: 1/40 (2013 Class)	09.2013—06.2018
	SKILLS
Adobe sets   AutoCad   Microsoft sets   Rhino   Grasshopper   SketchUp   Rendering	Software
Revit   Robotics   Python   Java English   Chinese	Language
	EXPERIENCES
Playze Architecture Consultant Company, Shanghai   Architect Intern - Collaborated with architects in multiple groups - In charge of research, basic drawing, 3d modeling, strategy discussion and documentation Led a pre-investigation of a commercial renovation project, helped partners to fast focus on target customer group and design goal.	06.2017—03.2018 get
Construction Experiment: Material, Structure and Tectonic   Research Assistant - Instructed junior students to build temporary constructions on campus Categorized and analyzed sophomores' works over years and made a publication.	09.2016—06.2017
O Architecture Design Studio, Shanghai   Interior Design Assistant - Developed a detailed 1:20 model for interior design by doing various material trials and using spectools such as polishing machine and heating wire cutting machine Product was used for exhibition.	01.2016—06.2017 ial
Shanghai Ancient Towns' Conservation and Renovation, Shanghai   Research Assistant - Interviewed citizens lived in Zhu Family Settlement Accomplished drawings and 3D models and studied conservation and restoration policy Won first prize of Summer Social Practice of SJTU.	07.2016—08.2016
Future Architects Association, Shanghai   Student Leader - Led post design, logo design and T-Shirt design Conducted promotion work and allocated tasks to members.	09.2013—06.2015

	<b>HONORS &amp; AWARDS</b>
Excellent Graduation Design of school of architecture in SJTU (The first place)	06.2018
National Scholarship (The highest-class scholarship in China's university   twice)	09.2014 09.2016
First Prize of Department in Summer Social Practice of SJTU	10.2016
Third Class Prize in Competition of Southern Bridge Newcity Design Project	10.2016
Tung OOCL Scholarship (Awarded to top 2 student of the department)	09.2015
First Prize in BIM Contest held by Tekla Co., Ltd.	08.2015
- Collaborated across majors to do a high-rise building modeling.	
- Built up framework in advance and helped partners to better understand the building.	
Excellent Student of Shanghai Jiao Tong University	10.2014
Second Prize in University Basketball Freshmen Cup	12.2013